AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records on Microfilm 5478 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records on Microfilm
1916-1968
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO)
AFL-CIO. Railway Employees' Department (RED)
5478 mf
12.33 cubic feet
111 microfilm reels
Microfilms, records (documents).
Amendments, Railroad records, Board of Mediation records, Mediation settlement records, meeting minutes, correspondence and office circulars
7858931
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 05, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 13, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Records of the Railway Employes' Department of the American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (RED). The RED was formed in 1908 to facilitate and coordinate the organizing activities and bargaining strategies of the seven national railroad shop craft unions.
The unions affiliated with RED included: the Brotherhood of Carmen of America; the International Association of Machinists; International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers, and Helpers; the International Brotherhood of Boilermakers; the Iron Shipbuilders and Helpers of America; the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; the International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers; and the Sheet Metal Workers International Association. Materials relating to the Machinists and Carmen predominate. The RED bargained with the railroad carriers for these skilled trade employees on a wide range of activities affecting almost every aspect of their social and economic status as employees.
Scope and Contents
A negative copy is available upon request.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5478: AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records
Arrangement
Series 13: Transportation Act, 1921-1928 Series 15: Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 Series 19: Cooperation, 1919-1933 Series 20: Federated Shop Craft Strike, 1922-1944 Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 Series 22: 1922 Strike Files, 1922-1925 Series 25: Master File of Official Circulars, 1916-1961
Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Political activity.; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States.; Railroad Shopmen's Strike, 1922.; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions --United States.; International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers.; AFL-CIO; AFL-CIO. Railway Employes' Department.; Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company.; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company.; Boston and Maine Railroad.; Brotherhood Railway Carmen of the United States and Canada.; Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company.; Chicago and North Western Railway Company.; Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway Company.; Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company.; International Association of Machinists.; International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers, and Helpers.; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers.; International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers.; Long Island Rail Road.; Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company.; Michigan Central Railroad Company.; Missouri, Kansas, and Texas Railway Company.; New York Central Railroad Company.; New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Company.; Norfolk and Western Railway Company.; Northern Pacific Railroad Company.; Pennsylvania Railroad.; Sheet Metal Workers' International Association.; Southern Pacific Railroad Company.; Union Pacific Railroad Company.; United States. Transportation Act, 1920.
7858931
- Sub-Series 13: Transportation Act, 1921-1928
  Scope and Contents
  Reels 1-4. Correspondence (carbons and originals), reports, petitions and printed legislative materials regarding hearings before the Senate Committee on Interstate Commerce on the Howell-Barkley Bill/Railway Labor Bill. Include testimony of labor leaders
  - Series 13: Transportation Act, 1921-1928 (Reel no.1) (Reel 1)
    - Guide to the entire collection., 1 (Reel 1)
    - Amendments, 1926; 2 (Reel 1)
      Code no. 35-26: January 4 - July 20, 1926.
    - Amendments, 1925; 3 (Reel 1)
      Code no. 35-26: August 27 - December 21, 1925.
    - Amendments, 1925; 4 (Reel 1)
      Code no. 35-26: January 1 - August 22, 1925.
  - Series 13: Transportation Act, 1921-1928 (Reel no.2) (Reel 2)
    - Amendments, 1924; 1 (Reel 2)
      Code no. 35-26: November 26 - December 30, 1924.
    - Amendments, 1924; 2 (Reel 2)
      Code no. 35-26: May 23 - November 25, 1924.
    - Amendments, 1924; 3 (Reel 2)
      Code no. 35-26: April 1 - May 22, 1924.
    - Amendments, 1924; 4 (Reel 2)
      Code no. 35-26; January 2 - March 31, 1924.
    - Amendments, 1923; 5 (Reel 2)
      Code no. 35-26: October 26 - December 31, 1923.
  - Series 13: Transportation Act, 1921-1928 (Reel no.3) (Reel 3)
    - Amendments, 1923; 1 (Reel 3)
      Code no. 35-26: July 14 - October 17, 1923.
    - Amendments, 1923; 2 (Reel 3)
      Code no. 35-26: June 30 - July 11, 1923.
    - Amendments, 1923; 3 (Reel 3)
      Code no. 35-26: April 19 - June 29, 1923.
  - Series 13: Transportation Act, 1921-1928 (Reel no.4) (Reel 4)
    - Amendments, 1923; 1 (Reel 4)
      Code no. 35-26: January 2 - April 18, 1923.
    - Amendments, 1920-1922; 2 (Reel 4)
      Code no. 35-26: February 14, 1920 - December 27, 1922.
    - Local Donations to National, 1924; 3 (Reel 4)
      Code no. 35-26: April 4 - September 3, 1924.
    - Potter Plan, 1925; 4 (Reel 4)
      Code no. 35-26A.
    - Miscellaneous Bills, Committee Reports and Congressional Testimony, 1920-1926; 5 (Reel 4)
      Code no. 35-26: Relating to the Howell-Barkley Bill.
    - Amendments, 6 (Reel 4)
      Code no.35-26: Partially dated.
    - Amendments, 7 (Reel 4)
      Code no. 35-26: Undated.
- Sub-Series 15: Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964
  Reels 5-16. Correspondence, case files, minutes, legal documents, pamphlets, clippings and statistical data regarding the activities of the United States National Mediation Board; the law suits brought before the National Railroad Adjustment Board; the Su
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.1) (Reel 5)
    - Proposed Amendments to the Railway Labor Act, 1933-1937; 1 (Reel 5)
      Code no. 35-64-Comm.: December 14, 1933 - May 27, 1937.
    - Proposed Amendments to the Railway Labor Act, 1928-1932; 2 (Reel 5)
      Code no. 35-64-Comm.: December 21, 1928 - November 22, 1932.
    - Proposed Amendments to the Railway Labor Act, 1926-1928; 3 (Reel 5)
      Code no. 35-64-Comm.: March 29, 1926 - December 20, 1928.
    - Amendments to the Railway Labor Act, 1934; 4 (Reel 5)
      Code no. 35-64-Comm. pt. 2: April 10, 1934 - May 31, 1934.
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.2) (Reel 6)
    - Amendments to the Railway Labor Act, 1933-1934; 1 (Reel 6)
      Code no. 35-64-Comm. pt. 2: December 14, 1933 - April 7, 1934.
    - Amendments to the Railway Labor Act, 1934-1941; 2 (Reel 6)
      Code no. 35-64-Comm. pt. 3: June 11, 1934 - September 5, 1941.
    - Amendments to the Railway Labor Act, 1934; 3 (Reel 6)
      Code no. 35-64-Comm. pt. 3: February 19, 1934 - June 9, 1934.
    - Railway Labor Act: National Mediation Board, 1944; 4 (Reel 6)
      Code no. 35-64-General: May 2, 1944 - December 29, 1944.
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.3) (Reel 7)
    - Railway Labor Act: National Mediation Board, 1940-1944; 1 (Reel 7)
      Code no. 35-64-General: June 30, 1940 - January 25, 1944.
    - Railway Labor Act: National Mediation Board, 1921-1940; 2 (Reel 7)
      Code no. 35-64-General: March 23, 1921 - June 12, 1940.
    - Railway Labor Act: National Mediation Board, 1947-1949; 3 (Reel 7)
      Code no. 35-64-General pt. 2: April 1, 1947 - December 8, 1949.
    - Railway Labor Act: National Mediation Board, 1945-1947; 4 (Reel 7)
      Code no. 35-64-General pt. 2: January 26, 1945 - March 28, 1947.
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.4) (Reel 8)
    - Railway Labor Act: National Mediation Board, 1945; 1 (Reel 8)
      Code no. 35-64-General pt. 2: January 1, 1945 - January 24, 1945.
    - Revision of Railway Labor Act, 1950; 2 (Reel 8)
      Code no. 35-64 pt. 3: May 4, 1950 - August 16, 1950.
    - Revision of Railway Labor Act, 1949-1950; 3 (Reel 8)
      Code no. 35-64 pt.3: December 31, 1949 - May 2, 1950
    - Railway Labor Act, 1950-1951; 4 (Reel 8)
      Code no. 35-64 pt.4: August 16, 1950 - January 4, 1951
    - Railway Labor Act, 1950; 5 (Reel 8)
      Code no. 35-64 pt.4: May 31, 1950 - August 9, 1950
    - Railway Labor Act, 1953-1956; 6 (Reel 8)
      Code no. 35-64 pt.5: National Mediation Board - March 4, 1953 - November 9, 1956
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.5) (Reel 9)
    - Railway Labor Act: National Mediation Board, 1950-1953; 1 (Reel 9)
      Code no. 35-64 pt.5: November 30, 1950 - February 28, 1953
    - Railway Labor Act, 1960-1964; 2 (Reel 9)
      Code no. 35-64 pt.6: August 10, 1960 - July 14, 1964
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.6) (Reel 10)
    - Railway Labor Act, 1957-1960; 1 (Reel 10)
      Code no. 35-64 pt.6: January 23, 1957 - June 28, 1960
    - Railway Labor Act: National Mediation Board, 1968; 2 (Reel 10)
      Code no. 35-64 pt.7: August 12, 1968 - December 6, 1968
    - Railway Labor Act: National Mediation Board, 1966-1968; 3 (Reel 10)
      Code no. 35-64 pt.7: June 30, 1966 - May 24, 1968
    - Railway Labor Act: National Mediation Board, 1964-1966; 4 (Reel 10)
      Code no. 35-64 pt.7:August 31, 1964 - June 22, 1966
    - Railway Labor Act: Definitions, 1926-1927; 5 (Reel 10)
      Code no. 35-64-1: June 18, 1926 - May 1, 1927
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.7) (Reel 11)
    - Railway Labor Act: General Duties, 1930-1938; 1 (Reel 11)
      Code no. 35-64-2: June 4, 1930 - July 6, 1938
    - Railway Labor Act: General Duties, 1926-1930; 2 (Reel 11)
      Code no. 35-64-2: June 9, 1926 - June 3, 1930
    - Railway Labor Act: Boards of Adjustment, 1926-1938; 3 (Reel 11)
      Code no. 35-64-3: May 31, 1926 - January 3, 1938
    - Railway Labor Act: General: Board of Mediation, 1934-1937; 4 (Reel 11)
      Code no. 35-64-4 pt.1: January 5, 1934 - December 27, 1937
    - Railway Labor Act: General: Board of Mediation, 1928-1933; 5 (Reel 11)
      Code no. 35-64-4 pt.1: March 21, 1928 - December 27, 1933
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.8) (Reel 12)
    - Railway Labor Act - General - Board of Mediation, 1926-1928; 1 (Reel 12)
      Code no. 35-64-4 pt.1: July 9, 1926 - February 18, 1928
    - Railway Labor Act - General - Board of Mediation, 1942-1944; 2 (Reel 12)
      Code no. 35-64-4 pt.2: April 29, 1942 - December 29, 1944
    - Railway Labor Act - General - Board of Mediation, 1940-1942; 3 (Reel 12)
      Code no. 35-64-4 pt.2: January 19, 1940 - April 27, 1942
    - Railway Labor Act - General - Board of Mediation, 1938-1939; 4 (Reel 12)
      Code no. 35-64-4 pt.2: January 4, 1938 - August 5, 1939
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.9) (Reel 13)
    - Railway Labor Act: General: Board of Mediation, 1951-1956; 1 (Reel 13)
      Code no. 35-64-4 pt.3: January 9, 1951 - November 27, 1956
    - Railway Labor Act: General: Board of Mediation, 1945-1950; 2 (Reel 13)
      Code no. 35-64-4 pt.3: January 24, 1945 - December 31, 1950
    - Rehabilitation of National Mediation Board, 1942; 3 (Reel 13)
      Code no. 35-64-4A Comm.: Railway Labor Executives Association
    - Briefs Submitted to National Mediation Board, 1941; 4 (Reel 13)
      Code no. 35-64-4A: October 13, 1934 - March 14, 1941
    - Board of Mediation Settlements re RED workers, 1926-1945; 5 (Reel 13)
      Code no. 35-64-5-1: Dispatchers, Sleeping Car Conductors, Shopmen, Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.10) (Reel 14)
    - Board of Mediation Settlements re RED workers, 1926-1945; 1 (Reel 14)
      Code no. 35-64-5-1: Order of Railway Conductors, Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, the Order of Railroad Telegraphers, Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way, Masters, Mates, and Pilots of America
    - Agreements by Direct Negotiations, 1926-1930; 2 (Reel 14)
      Code no. 35-64-5-2
    - Railway Labor Act: Section 6, 3 (Reel 14)
      Code no. 35-64-6
    - Correspondence re "Who's Who" (Arbitrators), 1928-1935; 4 (Reel 14)
      Code no. 35-64-8
    - Agreements to Arbitrate, 1926-1951; 5 (Reel 14)
      Code no. 35-64-8: Pam Am Flight-Engineers, Switchmen's Union of North America, International Association of Machinists, American Train Dispatcher's Association, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors and Brotherhood o
    - Arbitration Awards, 1926-1951; 6 (Reel 14)
      Code no. 35-64-8-1: International Longshoremen's Association, Airline Dispatcher's Association, Flight Communications Officers Association, Air Lines Communications Employees Association, Air Lines Pilots Association, Flight Engineer's International Assoc
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.11) (Reel 15)
    - Arbitration Awards, 1926-1951; 1 (Reel 15)
      Code no. 35-64-8-1: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen (cont.), Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks
    - Arbitration Awards, 1926-1951; 2 (Reel 15)
      Code no. 35-64-8-1: American Train Dispatcher's Association, Order of Railroad Telegraphers, Railway Signalmen of America, Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers and Helpers, International Brotherhood of Team
    - Shipbuilding Workers of America, Sheetmetal Workers International Association, Railroad Yardmasters of America, Air Line Mechanics, Air Line Meteorologists Association, 3 (Reel 15)
      Code no. 35-64-8- 1
    - Mediation Agreements by Union, 1935-1942; 4 (Reel 15)
      Code no. 35-64-8-1: Airline Pilots Association, Allied Craft Group Employees, American Railway Supervisors Association, Air Line Mechanics Association International, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America,
  - Series 15: The Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964 (Reel no.12) (Reel 16)
    - Mediation Agreements by Union, 1935-1942; 1 (Reel 16)
      Code no. 35-64-8-1: American Train Dispatcher's Association, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, International Longshoremen's Association, Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees
    - Mediation Agreements by Union, 1935-1942; 2 (Reel 16)
      Code no. 35-64-8-1: Seafarer's Union of North America and Sailors Union of Great Lakes, National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, National Maritime Union, National Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots of America, Railway Employees Department
    - Mediation Agreements by Union, 3 (Reel 16)
      Code no. 35-64-8-1: United Transport Service Employees of America, Order of Railway Conductors, Railroad Yardmasters of North America, Railroad Labor Executive's Committee, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Locomotive Engineers, Locomotive Firemen and Eng
    - Board of Mediation: Determination of Craft or Class, 4 (Reel 16)
      Code no. 35-64-8-1:
    - Mediation Board: Dismissals, 5 (Reel 16)
      Code no. 35-64-8-1
    - Mediation Board: Findings Upon Investigations, 6 (Reel 16)
    - Mediation Board: Notice of Hearings, 7 (Reel 16)
    - Mediation Board: Withdrawals and Investigations, 8 (Reel 16)
- Sub-Series 19: Cooperation, 1919-1933
  Reels 17-20. Correspondence, minutes, reports, proposals, and financial records regarding the cooperative movement within the railroad industry. Includes discussions of the Baltimore and Ohio (B&O) Plan; methods of improving railroad ship production; disc
  - Series 19: Cooperation, 1919-1933 (Reel no.1) (Reel 17)
    - General Co-operation File, 1926; 1 (Reel 17)
      Code no. 36-1: January 16, 1926 - October 30, 1926
    - General Co-operation File, 1925; 2 (Reel 17)
      Code no. 36-1: February 11, 1925 - December 30, 1925
    - General Co-operation File, 1919-1924; 3 (Reel 17)
      Code no. 36-1: November 10, 1919 - November 20, 1924
    - General Co-operation File, 1929-1930; 4 (Reel 17)
      Code no. 36-1 pt.2: August 20, 1929 - December 29, 1930
  - Series 19: Cooperation, 1919-1933 (Reel no.2) (Reel 18)
    - General Co-operation File, 1928-1929; 1 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-1 pt.2: January 3, 1928 - August 10, 1929
    - General Co-operation File, 1926-1927; 2 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-1 pt.2: February 18, 1926 - December 21, 1927
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 3 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: Management and Employees of Chillicothe, Ohio Shops, January 7, 1925 - March 4, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 4 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: Cleveland Terminal Shops, January 7, 1925 - March 4, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 5 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: Cone Shops, January 7, 1925 - March 4, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 6 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: Flora, Illinois, January 7, 1925 - March 19, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 7 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: Garnett, Indiana, January 7, 1925 - March 18, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 8 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: Hamilton, Ohio, January 7, 1925 - March 18, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 9 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: Dayton, Ohio, January 7, 1925 - March 24, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 10 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: Ivorydale, Ohio, January 7, 1925 - March 4, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 11 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: Lima, Ohio, April 7, 1924 - March 7, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 12 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: Storrs, Ohio, January 7, 1925 - February 9, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 13 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: Mount Clare Shops, January 7, 1925 - March 4, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 14 (Reel 18)
      Code no. 36-2: New Castle Junction, PA, January 7, 1925 - March 6, 1925
  - Series 19: Cooperation, 1919-1933 (Reel no.3) (Reel 19)
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 1 (Reel 19)
      Code no. 36-2: Newark Shop, January 21, 1925 - March 4, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 2 (Reel 19)
      Code no. 36-2: Toledo, Ohio, January 7, 1925 - March 18, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 3 (Reel 19)
      Code no. 36-2: Willard, Ohio, January 7, 1925 - March 4, 1925
    - Minutes and Record of Proceedings of Meeting of Co-operative Plan, 1925; 4 (Reel 19)
      Code no. 36-2: Zanesville, Ohio, January 7, 1925 - March 18, 1925
    - Withdrawal of Machinists from Co-operative Meetings, 1925; 5 (Reel 19)
      Code no. 36-2: Cumberland, Ohio - July 25, 1925 - August 3, 1925
    - Philadelphia: Activities of System Federation, 1925; 6 (Reel 19)
      Code no. 36-2: Executive Board on Wage and Rule Conference - June 25, 1925 - August 3, 1925
    - Miscellaneous Material on Union Management Co-operation, 1922-1925; 7 (Reel 19)
      Code no. 36-2
    - Baltimore & Ohio Co-operation: Maintenance of Way, 1931; 8 (Reel 19)
      Code no. 36-2-A-2: June 19, 1931 - July 23, 1931
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad Co-operation, 1923-1933; 9 (Reel 19)
      Code no. 36-4: November 24, 1923 - April 18, 1933
    - Canadian National Co-operation, 1927-1930; 10 (Reel 19)
      Code no. 36-6: October 5, 1927 - December 29, 1930
  - Series 19: Cooperation, 1919-1933 (Reel no.4) (Reel 20)
    - Canadian National Co-operation, 1924-1927; 1 (Reel 20)
      Code no. 36-6: August 30, 1924 - September 30, 1927
    - Canadian National Co-operation, 1923-1924; 2 (Reel 20)
      Code no. 36-6: January 5, 1923 - August 23, 1924
    - Canadian National Railways: Maintenance of Way Co-operation, 1924-1932; 3 (Reel 20)
      Code no. 36-6-A-2: August 23, 1924 - August 9, 1932
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Co-operation, 1924-1933; 4 (Reel 20)
      Code no. 36-8: January 22, 1924 - December 31, 1933
    - Seaboard Air Line Railway Company Co-operation, 1924-1931; 5 (Reel 20)
      Code no. 36-12:May 15, 1924 - November 10, 1931
    - Undated and miscellaneous documents, 6 (Reel 20)
      Code no. 36-6
- Sub-Series 20: Federated Shop Craft Strike, 1922-1944
  Reels 21-25. Correspondence, clippings, telegrams, and reports regarding the largest national railroad strike since the Pullman Strike of 1894. The strike was not settled until 1924 and some issues lingered on for decades. Includes detailed reports, reque
  - Series 20: Federated Shop Crafts Strike, 1922-1944 (Reel no.1) (Reel 21)
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1923-1924; 1 (Reel 21)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: March 14, 1923 - July 18, 1924
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1923; 2 (Reel 21)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: February 1, 1923 - February 28, 1923
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1923; 3 (Reel 21)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: January 1, 1923 - January 31, 1923
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 4 (Reel 21)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: December 2, 1922 - December 31, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 5 (Reel 21)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: November 1, 1922 - November 29, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 6 (Reel 21)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: October 12, 1922 - October 31, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 7 (Reel 21)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: September 25, 1922 - October 11, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 8 (Reel 21)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: September 19, 1922 - September 24, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 9 (Reel 21)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: September 11, 1922 - September 18, 1922
  - Series 20: Federated Shop Crafts Strike, 1922-1944 (Reel no.2) (Reel 22)
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 1 (Reel 22)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: September 1, 1922 - September 10, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 2 (Reel 22)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: August 1, 1922 - August 17, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 3 (Reel 22)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: July 17, 1922 - July 31, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 4 (Reel 22)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: July 15, 1922 - July 16, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 5 (Reel 22)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: July 14, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 6 (Reel 22)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: July 12, 1922 - July 13, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 7 (Reel 22)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: July 10, 1922 - July 11, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 8 (Reel 22)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: July 7, 1922 - July 9, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 9 (Reel 22)